nyhabitat.com 2019-12-12

# New York Habitat's Privacy Policy

### Our Commitment to Privacy and Reliability

**By using this Website, you expressly agree to this Privacy Policy.**

**Your privacy is important to us**. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

**The Information We Collect**. This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the **New York Habitat** 's Website. On some pages you can make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected on these pages are:

> Name   
>  Occupation   
>  Email address   
>  Phone and Fax number 

### The way we use cookies

Cookies are small pieces of information that some websites ask to store on (and later retrieve from) your computer. When you visit New York Habitat's Website, cookies are stored into your browser, provided your browser accepts them. The information stored on those cookies contains a randomly generated string but no personal information. Those cookies will allow you to retrieve previously selected preferences (if any) each time you come back visiting our website. Additionally, we may use cookies and third parties applications from time to time to build statistics using information such as browser, URL, IP address.

### The way we protect your privacy

We use the information you provide about yourself when placing a request only to complete that request. **We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete a transaction**. We use return email addresses to answer the emails we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.

You can register with our website if you would like to receive specific information as well as general updates on company news and services. Information you submit on our website will not be used for this purpose unless you fill out the registration form.

We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals.

Finally, **we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described**.

### Our commitment to security

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

### Our commitment to children privacy

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information on our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13. If and when it is discovered that a registration form or any other information has been submitted by an individual under the age of 13, New York Habitat deletes it immediately.

### General Data Protection Regulation

The General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) is a European Union law which gives individuals the right to know which personal information is collected and processed and for which purpose. Under this regulation, you have the right to request access to this data, correct it as well as withdraw your consent to process it or have it erased. For any questions related to your personal data, please call us at +1 (212) 255-8018[+1 (212) 255-8018](tel:+1-212-255-8018) or send us an email to [privacy@nyhabitat.com](mailto:privacy@nyhabitat.com).

### Where we process your personal information

**For those of you visiting us from the European Union, Canada, or other jurisdictions outside of the United States, please note that the personal information you enter may be transferred outside of your home country for use by New York Habitat for one or more of the purposes described in this policy. Your information may be processed and stored in the United States and as a result, governments, courts or law enforcement or regulatory agencies may be able to obtain the disclosure of your information through laws applicable in the United States. By using our website and providing us with your personal information, you consent to this transfer of your personal information.**

### Updates to this Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy was last updated on November 21 2019.  This Privacy Policy applies from that date.  We may occasionally amend this Privacy Policy to reflect regulatory requirements, advances in technology, Website updates and changes in our information collection and disclosure practices. Any new policy will automatically be effective when it is published on the website. You should therefore return here regularly to view our most up to date Privacy Policy.

### How to contact us

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please call us at +1 (212) 255-8018[+1 (212) 255-8018](tel:+1-212-255-8018) or send us an email to [privacy@nyhabitat.com](mailto:privacy@nyhabitat.com).
